<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="text">play_newsstand  Top stories
        person  For you   star_border  Following
        search  Saved searches    flag  India   public  World
        room  Your local news   business  Business   memory  Technology
        theaters  Entertainment   directions_bike  Sports   experiment  Science
        fitness_center  Health    Language region English (India)   Settings
        Get the Android app  open_in_new   Get the iOS app  open_in_new
        Send feedback   Help  open_in_new  Privacy · Terms · About Google
        Headlines  More Headlines   Death toll risen to 304 due to China\'s
        coronavirus. (File)  Coronavirus Updates: India Suspends Online Visa
        For Chinese Citizens, Foreigners Living In China  India reported its
        second case of coronavirus in Kerala, where the first case of the inf
        ectious disease, which has killed over 300 people in China, was reported
        ...   NDTV News • 8 minutes ago    bookmark_border  share  more_vert
        Second case of coronavirus confirmed in Kerala  India News: India on
        Sunday reported a second case of novel coronavirus with a person from
        Kerala with a travel history to China testing positive. The patient i
        s.   Times of India • 4 hours ago    bookmark_border  share  more_ver
        t   Coronavirus Outbreak LIVE: India Temporarily Suspends Online Vis
        a for Chinese Citizens; 3 Hospitalised in Jaipur With Symptoms  Cor
        onavirus Outbreak LIVE Updates: Kerala today confirmed the second
        case of Coronavirus even as the death toll in China has increased
        to 304 with more ...   News18 • 17 minutes ago    bookmark_borde
        r  share  more_vert   Locked-down Wuhan will be a breeding groun
        d for fear and stigma  Last week the World ...   The Guardian •
        2 hours ago • Opinion    bookmark_border  share  more_vert   Cor
        onavirus: US and Australia close borders to Chinese arrivals  Co
        untries around the world have closed their borders to arrivals f
        rom China, as officials work to control the rapid spread of the
        . The US and Australia ...   BBC News • Yesterday    bookmark_border
        share  more_vert   View full coverage  keyboard_arrow_up    Can you c
        hoose between existing income tax regime and new optional regime eve
        ry year?  Budget 2020 has given taxpayers the option to continue with
        existing income tax slabs, rates, and exemptions or opt for the proposed new
        tax regime with lower ...   Economic Times • 1 hour ago    bookmark_border  s
        hare  more_vert    Budget 2020 | Feeling Unwell, Nirmala Sitharaman Cuts Shor
        t Longest-Ever Budget Speech   video_youtubeNDTV • Yesterday    bookmark_bord
        er  share  more_vert   View full coverage  keyboard_arrow_up    Hate speech:
        ‘Time to evict protestors in Delhi’, says BJP’s new campaign song  The Bhara
        tiya Janata Party continues to stoke hate and divisiveness in its election
        campaign in Delhi. At a time when two gunmen have fired at peaceful ...   S
        croll.in • Yesterday    bookmark_border  share  more_vert    \"Polls Come
        And Go\": Arvind Kejriwal\'s Dig At Amit Shah After Shooting  The shooting
        at Delhi\'s Shaheen Bagh -- the epicentre of the protests against the contentious Citizenship Amendment Act -- triggered a war of words between ...   NDTV News • Yesterday    bookmark_border  share  more_vert   View full coverage  keyboard_arrow_up Kerala reported first case of coronavirus on Thursday. (File)   India\'s Second Coronavirus Case In Kerala, Patient In Isolation At Hospital  India\'s second case of coronavirus has been reported in Kerala, three days after the southern state reported country\'s first case.   NDTV News • 2 hours ago      bookmark_border  share  more_vert    In Blow for NRIs, Those Not Paying Taxes Abroad Will Be Now Taxed in India  Revenue Secretary Ajay Bhushan Pandey said an Indian now has to stay abroad for 240 days, as against the 182 previously, to be categorised as a ...   News18 • Yesterday    bookmark_border  share  more_vert    Income tax highlights of Budget 2020  While there is no change in existing income-tax slab rates for individuals, a new tax regime has been proposed in Budget 2020, under which individual ...   Economic Times • 2 hours ago    bookmark_border  share  more_vert   View full coverage  keyboard_arrow_up  The four death row convicts were to be executed in Delhi’s Tihar jail on February 1 before a court on Friday stayed their executions. (HT Photo)  Tihar Jail to ask court for execution date for 2012 Delhi rape convicts  A day after a Delhi court stayed the black warrant for the execution of four death row convicts for the rape and murder of a 23-year-old paramedic in December ...   Hindustan Times • Yesterday    bookmark_border  share  more_vert    President rejects mercy plea of Nirbhaya case convict Vinay Kumar Sharma  Earlier, another convict Mukesh Singh had filed a mercy petition that was swiftly rejected by the President.   The Hindu • Yesterday    bookmark_border  share  more_vert   View full coverage  keyboard_arrow_up        Getting your weather...           C |F |K     In the news     B. S. Yediyurappa    New Zealand national cricket team    Jamia Millia Islamia    Bharatiya Janata Party    Hindu Mahasabha    Karnataka    Imran Khan    Pakistan    Coronavirus    Nirmala Sitharaman    o
    </string>


</resources>
